<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chess on Complexity</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/chess/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chess on Complexity</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/chess/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Civitanova Chess Tournament Round 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:09:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome back! Yesterday I was too tired to write this post, so I&amp;rsquo;m writing it now. This is the final game of the tournamente and I&amp;rsquo;m at 3/4 playing on second board and if a manage to win I guarantee a third place! However this didn&amp;rsquo;t affect my way too play, I was only focused on playing well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-game&#34;&gt;The game&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the final game I&amp;rsquo;m Black against Mauro Di Mantino, a 1984 rated player - and also born in 1984, how cool is that?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civitanova Chess Tournament Round 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:40:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome back! I have to admit, writing a post for every game is not easy, but it forces me to analyse and study it, so it is definitely worth it. And I hope you are appreciating this too!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Where were we? Last game was the amazing King&amp;rsquo;s Indian that unfortunately ended in a loss, so I&amp;rsquo;m at 2/3. I know it will be hard to reach the podium at this point, but all I care in the end is to play some good games.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civitanova Chess Tournament Round 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 19:45:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome back! Are you ready for a crazy King&amp;rsquo;s Indian game? This is the third round of the tournament, I&amp;rsquo;m at 2/2 on board two and I need a win to stay on top of the leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-game&#34;&gt;The Game&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m against Leonardo Renzetti, a player about my age but almost 100 rating points higher, at 2020 ELO. I&amp;rsquo;ve already analysed the game with an engine with him after we finished, but this time the vibes mean much more than engine&amp;rsquo;s evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civitanova Chess Tournament Round 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:48:08 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome back! Already here for round 2? This morning it was a quick game, so I should manage to publish this before the third round.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-game&#34;&gt;The game&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This time I had the white pieces against Corrado Luberti, a player at his very first tournament! I talked to him a little bit after the game and he confessed he doesn&amp;rsquo;t really like thinking too much at every move, but he wanted to give it a try anyway. Honestly I also wasn&amp;rsquo;t really in the mood to spend too much time, since today it is my brother&amp;rsquo;s birthday - 🥳🥳 - and we will go out for lunch - oh no, I still have only 20 minutes to write this post 😱.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civitanova Chess Tournament Round 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 20:50:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/civitanova-chess-tournament-round-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome back! I know, it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since my last post, but finding the time to write isn&amp;rsquo;t easy. Anyway, right now I&amp;rsquo;m back home in Marche for a few days and took the opportunity to play a chess tournament in Civitanova. Actually, I also played a tournament in Recco (Liguria) a couple of weeks ago and wanted to make a post about it, but didn&amp;rsquo;t have the time. However it went very badly, so you didn&amp;rsquo;t miss anything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Chess</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/back-to-chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:12:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/back-to-chess/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome back! I was writing a post on a chess tournament I played around a month ago, but in the end I decided to postpone it and instead focus first on what has been my journey and where I am now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will be a very personal post. Forgive me for the drastic change of tone there will be at some point, but to talk about the last part, I also wanted to talk about my past and this was the only way I could do it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
